this smart kind of tool, this very serious, you know, and very accurate and fact-based tool is
also another kind of AI chatbot. It's more of a search engine, right? But I do put it in the chatbots
category and perplexity is very useful and can be very useful, you know? A lot of the times,
it can be way more useful than other chatbots like Gemini and chat GPT that we use on a daily
basis as you see, especially when it comes to important information. So a lot of the times when
you're in chat GPT or any other kind of AI tool, you see that over there in the bottom, it says
chat GPT can make mistakes and check important information, right? But when it comes to perplexity,
they are trying their best not to make mistakes. So absolutely, perplexity may make mistakes as well.
But the point here is that it is focusing, so the identity of perplexity is about focusing on minimizing
these kind of mistakes and being as true as possible, being as fact-based as possible and being
as accurate as possible. So this was another smart AI tool, a pretty useful one for a lot of you guys,
I'm pretty sure. And that's all that we have for today with Para Plank City AI.